ACWA Photographs 5743 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACWA Photographs
1890-2002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
5743 P
32.33 cubic feet
32.3 linear ft.
Photographs.
Includes photos of national political figures, labor leaders and workers including many women workers in clothing and other industries, immigration, war effort, political work, union label campaigns, health care, child care, education, housing, clothing imports, organized by name and subject
5757429
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 04, 2008
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Scope and Contents
Includes photos of national political figures, labor leaders and workers including many women workers in clothing and other industries, immigration, war effort, political work, union label campaigns, health care, child care, education, housing, clothing imports, organized by name and subject
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records 5619 P: ACTWU Photographs 5619/027 P: ACTWU Communications and Public Relations Department Burt Beck Files Photographs 5743 P LS: ACWA Lantern Slides 5745 P: ACWA Publicity Department Photographs 5981 P: ACTWU Labor Unity Photograph Files 6015 P: ACWA Hyman Blumberg Photographs
Abramowitz, Abraham; Addeo, Benjamin; Agneta, Nic; Aeillo, Edmun; Ala, Domenic; Albet, Samuel; Aligwekwe, Evalyn; Altman, Hyman; Alvano, Vincent; Amato, Leonard; Amdur, Max; Anderson, Mildred; Arcomano, Frank; Arnone, Paul; Aronson, D.A.; August, Rebecca; Abquet, Albert; Barbeck, Mike; Barber, Minnie; Bardield, Leora; Barron, Sarah; Barton, Oma; Bartone, Salvatore; Batchelor, Neil; Baxter, Willie; Bayard, Alexis DuPont; Beck, Burt; Becker, Hyman; Bell, David; Bell, Jess A.; Bellanca, Dorothy; Bellia, Bruno; Benedict, Victor; Bergeron-Lebeuf, Gisele; Bernstein, Meyer; Blair, Ed; Blankenship, James; Bloch, Harry, 1946-; Block, Reuben; Bloom, Dora; Bluestein; Blumberg, Bessie; Blumberg, Hyman, 1885-1968; Blumberg, Hayman; Blume, Jacob; Blumenrich, Morris; Bonitt, Ed; Bookbinder, Hyman Harry, 1916-201; Borys, Jean; Brand, Morris A.; Brandwen, Maxwell; Brandzel, Sol; Brazier, Richard; Briskin, Dave; Brittingham, Helen; Brock, Lena; Brudo, Eva C.; Burr, Charles; Busillo, George; Calmus, Isaac; Campobasso, Lee; Cannarozzi, Nicola; Capizzi, James; Cardinale, Anthony; Castelluccio, A.; Catalaanotti, Joseph; Chapin, Louise; Chatman, Abraham; Churchwell, Aslee; Ciacco, Sam; Cohen, Alex; Coratolo, Michael; Cartigene, Anthony; Cox, Claude; Curcio, Anthony J.; Currie, Edgar; Cursi, Aldo; D'Alesandro, Thomas, 1903-1987; Daniel, R.K.; Davis, Bob; DeCosta, Carmen; DeDominicis, Ulisse; DeGirolomo, Ralph; Del Giacco, Charles; Del-Torto, Romeo; Deluca, Philip; Dick, Irwin; Dickason, Gladys; DiLauro, Thomas; Dispensa, Charles; Ditommaso, Vincent; Divinagracia, Clethra; Dollar, Gladys; Douglas, Roger, 1928-; Draper, Anne, 1917-1973; Dropkin, Henry; Durchslag, Sam; Elkuss, Bill; Ellstein, Jacob; Ervin, Charles W., -1953.; Faulo, John; Feder, Sam; Fiascone, Joseph; Finley, Murray, 1922-1995; Flavell, Tom; Fried, Milton; Fridman, Abe; Froise, Anthony; Frumererman, Harry; Galloway, Pauline; Gambino, Frank; Garloff, George; Garrahan, Mabel; Gassman, Murrya; Genis, Burton; Georgian, Angelo; Genis, Sander; Gersh, E.B.; Gibson, Kenneth A.; Gitelson, Alma; Giuliani, Albert; Goldberg, Louis, 1893-; Goldberg, Easer; Goldsmith, Harry; Goldsmith, Charles; Goldstein, Zelda; Gottesman, Edmon; Gottleib, Benjamin; Graham, James J.; Graomger, Walter; Grana, Neno; Grande, Anthony; Grandinetti, Emilio; Greco, Andrew; Greenbaum, Louis; Greenberg, Nat; Gregware, Roy; Guttway, Andrew; Hall, William C.; Hall, Bessie; Hanson, Alice; Harman, J.B.S.; Hatman, Arthur; Heimbach, Larry; Hemsing, Albert E.; Herman, Ben; Herman, Louis; Herman, Sam; Hershkoiwitz, S.; Hill, Rachel; Hillman, Sidney, 1887-1946; Hoag, Ray; Hoehn, G.A.; Hollander, Isadore; Hollander, Louis, 1893-; Holstein, Sam; Hopkins, Laveta; Horan, Edward; Horton, Paul; Janecek, Joseph; Jefcoats, Catherine; Jemmott, Bert; Jones, Isabele; Joseph, Delia; Kadish, Jack; Kaminsky, Joseph; Kamm, Reuben; Karmen, Murray; Kantrowitz, Isidore; Karson, Marc; Katz, Edward; Kelly, James E., -1946.; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963; Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968; Kilpatrick, Joan; Kirsch, Frank; Klass, Hyman; Klima, Jack; Koch, Frank; Kolkey, Sam; Krzycki, Leo; Kuhlman, Griselda; LaCapria, Vincent; Lalli, Victor; LaMar, Elden; Lamb, Carl; Langbord, J. A.; LaPenna, James; LaScala, Frank; LaScala, Sam; Lauria, John; Lautman, Harry; Lederman, Harry; Levin, Lawrence; Levin, Samuel; Levine, Abe; Licastro, Philip; Lifschitz, Jack; Linds, Saul; Linenberg, Cora; Lipsky, Joseph; Lipshutz, Julius; Lowther, Folly; Maietta, Julia; Maraviglia, Oswald; Marimpietri, A.D.; Markovitz, Harry; Marsella, Tom; Matthies, John; McCollum, Susi; McMahon, John; McGill, Eula; Meccia, Marco; Medora, Frank; Mehaffey, Nettie; Mendelson, Marvin; Menendez, Manuel; Merced, Efrain; Messian, Vincent; Miller, Herrill; Mindess, Nathan; Monas, David; Monat, Peter; Murphy, James, -1964.; Musch, August; Myers, Evelyn; Napolitano, Frank; Negro, Rocco; Nemser, Hyman; Ninno, Pat; Nisselson, Michael; Nocella, Sam; Norwitch, Harry; Nuttall, Alfred; Oliva, Joseph; Oswaldo, Eusepi; Panick, Frank; Panken, Jacob; Pappas, Costas; Parenti, Patsy; Patti, Joseph; Payne, Ruth V.; Pecoraro, Ralph J.; Peel, Elbert; Penn, Jane; Peppercorn, B.; Peppercorn, Max; Peta, Thomas; Peterson, Esther, 1906-1997.; Peito, Robert; Piepenhagen, A. G.; Polk, Leo; Posner, Jerome; Potofsky, Jacob S. (Jacob Samuel), 1894-1979; Prager, Jack; Previs, Joe; Rabkin, Elias; Ragnold, Fred; Redden, Jackson; Reiff, Hyman; Reimbold, William C.; Reiss, Raymond; Rheingold, Herman; Ricciardelli, Vincent; Richens, Sarah; Rissman, Sidney; Rocco, William; Roitman, Irving; Rosen, Morris; Rosenblum, Frank, 1888-1973; Rothbart, Isidore; Rozner, Sarah; Rudich, Philip; Salerno, Carmen; Samuel, Howard D.; Samuel, Ralph; Santora, Mami; Schevetsky, N.; Schlossberg, Joseph, 1875-1971; Schneid, Hyman; Schubert, Joseph; Schultheis, Ed; Schultz, Louis; Schwartz, Ernest; Seibert, Henry; Seitchik, Joseph; Selm, Fred; Senecal, J. M.; Serafini, Henry; Sheinkman, Jacob; Shoaff, James; Shucker, George; Siegel, Lewis; Siegel, Nathann; Silver, Murray; Silverman, Abe; Skala, Stephen; Smith, Samuel; Sneed, Geneva; Dobczak, John; Sobieski, Frank; Soden, Roy; Spitzer, Morris; Spivak, S.; Steinberg, Martin; Stone, M. Hedley; Strebel, Gustave A.; Sweeney, Annie Belle; Swoboda, Pete; Tomarken, Morris; Troisi, Ralph; Tupper, Rodney; Wachtel, Mitchell; Wallace, Anna; Weinstein, Charles; Weinstein, Florence; Weinstein, Murray; Wisgal, Isador; Welker, Helen; Wertheimer, Valentin; Wyss, Harold; Yannetti, Louis; Zubal, Pete; Zusman, Morris; Zwickel, Aaron; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union
5757429
- Abramowitz, Abraham (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Addeo, Benjamin (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Agneta, Nick (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Aiello, Edmund (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Ala, Domenic (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Albet, Samuel (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Aligwekwe, Evalyn (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Altman, Hyman (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Alvano, Vincent (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Scope and Contents
  See also Box 56, ff1
- Amato, Leonard (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Amdur, Max (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Anderson, Mildred (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Arcomano, Frank (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Arnone, Paul (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Aronson, D.A. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- August, Rebecca (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Abquet, Albert (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Barbeck, Mike (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Barber, Minnie (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Bardield, Leora (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Barron, Sarah (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Barton, Oma (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Bartone, Salvatore (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Batchelor, Nell (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Baxter, Willie (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Bayard, Alexis DuPont (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Beck, Burt (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Becker, Hyman (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Bell, David (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Bell, Jess A. (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Bellanca, August (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Bellanca, Dorothy Jacobs (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Bellia, Bruno (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Benedict, Victor (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Bergeron-Lebeuf, Gisele (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Bernecker, Dr. (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Bernstein, Meyer (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Blair, Ed (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Blankenship, James (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Bloch, Harry (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Block, Reuben (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Bloom, Dora (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Bluestein (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Blumberg, Bessie (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Blumberg, Hyman [folder 1 of 6] (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Blumberg, Hyman [folder 2 of 6] (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Blumberg, Hyman [folder 3 of 6] (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Blumberg, Hyman [folder 4 of 6] (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Blumberg, Hyman [folder 5 of 6] (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Blumberg, Hyman [folder 6 of 6] (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Blume, Jacob (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Blumenrich, Morris (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Bonitt, Ed (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Bookbinder, Hyman (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Borys, Jean (Box 2, Folder 7)
  See also Box 56, ff2
- Brand, Dr. Morris A. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Brandwen, Maxwell [folder 1 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Brandwen, Maxwell [folder 2 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Brandwen, Maxwell [folder 3 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Brandzel, Sol (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Brazier, Richard (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Briskin, Dave (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Brittingham, Helen (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Brock, Lena (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Bross, Maurice (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Burdo, Eva C. (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Burr, Charles (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Busillo, George (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Calmus, Isaac (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Campobasso, Lee (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Cannarozzi, Nicola (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Cannizzaro, James V. (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Capizzi, James (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Cardinale, Anthony (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Castelluccio, A. (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Catalaanotti, Joseph (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Chaney, David (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Chapin, Louise (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Chatman, Abraham [folder 1 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Chatman, Abraham [folder 2 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Churchwell, Aslee (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Ciacco, Sam (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Cohen, Alex (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Cohen, Jack (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Cohen, Julius (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Cohen, Sammy (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Cooper, John H. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  empty
- Coratolo, Michael (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Cartigene, Anthony (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Cox, Claude (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Curcio, Anthony J. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Currie, Edgar (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Cursi, Aldo (Box 3, Folder 9)
- DAlesandro, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Daniel, R.K. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Davis, Bob (Box 3, Folder 12)
- DeCosta, Carmen (Box 3, Folder 13)
- DeDominicis, Ulisse (Box 3, Folder 14)
- DeGirolomo, Ralph (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Del Giacco, Charles (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Del-Torto, Romeo (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Deluca, Philip (Box 3, Folder 18)
- DeMare, Patrick (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Dial, John H., Jr. (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Dick, Irwin (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Dickason, Gladys [folder 1 of 2], 1948 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  1948 and others. See also Box 56, ff2
- Dickason, Gladys [folder 2 of 2], 1948 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- DiLauro, Thomas A. (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Dispensa, Charles (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Ditommaso, Vincent (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Divinagracia, Clethra (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Dollar, Gladys (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Dorfman, Joseph (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Douglas, Roger (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Draper, Anne (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Dropkin, Henry - Empty (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Durchslag, Sam (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Elkuss, Bill (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Ellstein, Jacob (Box 3, Folder 35)
- English, Charles (Box 3, Folder 36)
  See also Box 56, ff3
- Ervin, Charles W. [folder 1 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Ervin, Charles W. [folder 2 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Ervin, Charles W. [folder 3 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Faulo, John (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Feder, Sam (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Fiascone, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Finley, Murray (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Also includes Jack Sheinkman, George McGovern, George Meany
- Fisher, C. Edmund (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Fisher, Lena Local 506 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Flavell, Tom (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Ford, Lawrence (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Fox, Sam (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Francasio (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Frankel, Julius (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Freedman (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Fried, Milton (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Friedman, Abe (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Froise, Anthony (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Frumererman, Harry (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Galloway, Pauline (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Gambino, Frank (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Garloff, George (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Garrahan, Charles [folder 1 of 2] (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Garrahan, Charles [folder 2 of 2] (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Garrahan, Mabel (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Gassman, Murrya (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Genis, Burton (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Genis, Sander (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Georgian, Angelo (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Gersh, E.B. (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Gibson, Kenneth A. (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Gitelson, Alma (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Giuliani, Albert (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Giunta, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Gold, Joe (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Goldberg, Easer (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Golberg, Louis (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Goldsmith, Harry (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Goldsmith, Charles (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Goldstein, Zelda (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Gottesman, Edmon (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Gottleib, Benjamin (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Graham, James J. (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Graomger, Walter (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Grana, Neno (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Grande, Anthony (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Grandinetti, Emilio (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Greco, Andrew (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Greenbaum, Louis (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Greenberg, Nat (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Gregware, Roy (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Guttay, Andrew (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Hall, William C. (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Hall, Bessie (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Hanley, Frank (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Hanson, Alice (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Harman, J.B.S. (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Hartman, Arthur (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Hawes, Elizabeth (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Heimbach, Larry (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Hemsing, Albert E. (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Herman, Ben (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Herman, Louis (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Herman, Sam (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Hershkoiwitz, S. (Box 5, Folder 18(a))
- Hill, Rachel (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 1 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 20)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff4
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 2 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 21)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff5
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 3 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 22)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff6
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 4 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 23)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff7
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 5 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 24)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff8
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 6 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 25)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff9
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 7 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 26)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff10
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 8 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 27)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff11
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 9 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 28)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff12
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 10 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 29)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff13
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 11 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 30)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff14
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 12 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 31)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff15
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 13 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 32)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff16
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 14 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 33)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff17
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 15 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 34)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff18
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 16 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 35)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff19
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 17 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 36)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff20
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 18 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 37)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff21
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 19 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 38)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff22
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 20 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 39)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff23
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 21 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 40)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff24
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 22 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 41)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff25
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 23 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 42)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff26
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 24 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 43)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff27
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 25 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 44)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff28
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 26 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 45)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff29
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 27 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 46)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff30
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 28 of 53] (Box 5, Folder 47)
  includes list of former file folder headings. See also Box 56, ff31
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 29 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 1)
  listed by subject. See also Box 56, ff4
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 30 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 31 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 32 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 33 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 34 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 35 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 36 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 37 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 38 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 39 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 40 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 41 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 42 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 43 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 44 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 45 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 46 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 47 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 48 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 49 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 50 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 51 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 52 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Hillman, Sidney [folder 53 of 53] (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Hoag, Ray (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Hoehn, G.A. (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Hoffman (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Hollander, Isadore (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Hollander, Louis [folder 1 of 10] (Box 6, Folder 30)
  See also Box 56, ff4
- Hollander, Louis [folder 2 of 10] (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Hollander, Louis [folder 3 of 10] (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Hollander, Louis [folder 4 of 10] (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Hollander, Louis [folder 5 of 10] (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Hollander, Louis [folder 6 of 10] (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Hollander, Louis [folder 7 of 10] (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Hollander, Louis [folder 8 of 10] (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Hollander, Louis [folder 9 of 10] (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Hollander, Louis [folder 10 of 10] (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Holstein, Sam (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Hopkins, Laveta (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Hopkins, Leon (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Horan, Edward (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Horn (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Horton, Paul (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Jackson, James (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Janecek, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Jefcoats, Catherine (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Jemmott, Bert (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Jodoin, Claude (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Jones, Dorothy (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Jones, Isabele (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Joseph, Delia (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Kadish, Jack (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Kaminsky, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Kamm, Reuben (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Kantrowitz, Isadore (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Karmen, Murray (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Karson, Marc (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Katz, Edward (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Kelly, James E. (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Kennedy (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Kilpatrick, Joan (Box 7, Folder 24)
- King, Charles (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Kirsch, Frank (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Klass, Hyman (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Klima, Jack (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Koch, Frank (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Kolkey, Sam (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Kopelov, Connie (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Kopita, Murry (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Krips, Sam (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Kroll, Jack [folder 1 of 7] (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Kroll, Jack [folder 2 of 7] (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Kroll, Jack [folder 3 of 7] (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Kroll, Jack [folder 4 of 7] (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Kroll, Jack [folder 5 of 7] (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Kroll, Jack [folder 6 of 7] (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Kroll, Jack [folder 7 of 7] (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Krzycki, Leo (Box 7, Folder 41)
  See also Box 56, ff5
- Kuhlman, Griselda (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Labine, Clem (Box 7, Folder 43)
- LaCapria, Vincent [folder 1 of 2] (Box 7, Folder 44)
- LaCapria, Vincent [folder 2 of 2] (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Lalli, Victor (Box 7, Folder 46)
- LaMar, Elden (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Lamb, Carl (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Langbord, Dr. J.A. (Box 7, Folder 49)
- LaPenna, James (Box 7, Folder 50)
- LaScala, Frank (Box 7, Folder 51)
- LaScala, Sam (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Lauria, John (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Lautman, Harry (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Lederman, Harry (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Levin, Lawrence (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Levin, Robert (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Levin, Samuel [folder 1 of 4] (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Levin, Samuel [folder 2 of 4] (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Levin, Samuel [folder 3 of 4] (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Levin, Samuel [folder 4 of 4] (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Levine, Abe (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Levy, Leonard (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Lewis, John L. (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Licastro, Philip (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Lifshitz, Jack (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Linds, Saul (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Linenberg, Cora (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Lipsky, Joseph (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Lipshutz, Julius (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Lowther, Dollie [Robinson] (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Maietta, Julia (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Mann, Michael (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Maraviglia, Oswald (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Marimpietri, A.D. (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Markovitz, Harry (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Marsella, Tom (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Matthies, John (Box 8, Folder 23)
- McCollum, Susi (Box 8, Folder 24)
- McMahon, John (Box 8, Folder 25)
- McGill, Eula (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Meccia, Marco (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Medora, Frank (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Mehaffey, Nettie (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Mendelson, Marvin (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Menendez, Manuel (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Merced, Efrain (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Messian, Vincent (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Miller, Abraham [folder 1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 34)
  See also Box 56, ff6
- Miller, Abraham [folder 2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Miller, Joyce [folder 1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Miller, Joyce [folder 2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Miller, Herrill (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Miller, Ruth (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Miller, Vera [folder 1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Miller, Vera [folder 2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Mindess, Nathan (Box 8, Folder 42)